[
  {
    "question": "Is this a new question?",
    "answer": "New answer",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the word Halloween mean?",
    "answer": "All Saints' Eve",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the origin of the carved pumpkin at Halloween?",
    "answer": "Legend of Jack-o'-lantern",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mythical creature transforms into a wolf during a full moon?",
    "answer": "Werewolf",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What plant protects homes from evil spirits?",
    "answer": "Rue",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the origin of dressing up on Halloween?",
    "answer": "To scare away evil spirits",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country did the celebration of Halloween originate?",
    "answer": "Ireland",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the Celtic festival that gave rise to Halloween called?",
    "answer": "Samhain",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "question": "What popular Halloween figure is associated with black cats?",
    "answer": "Witches",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the relationship between Halloween and the Day of the Dead?",
    "answer": "Both celebrate the dead, but in different cultures",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What supernatural being is said to emerge from its grave on Halloween?",
    "answer": "Zombie",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this a new question?",
    "answer": "New answer",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is Bigfoot a giant?",
    "answer": "It's a giant monster",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  }
]